≡

Returning Veterans Project

*  Search 

Close

Search Search Search 

    About

    Get Services

    Volunteer Providers

    Help RVP

    News

    Events

Privacy Statement
=================

We have established policies to protect the security and privacy of all information we collect. We maintain strict internal policies against unauthorized disclosure or use of any client or website user information. Any suspected attempt to breach our policies and procedures, or to engage in any type of unauthorized action involving our web systems will be regarded as potential criminal activity and may be reported to the appropriate authorities.

Social Media Policy
-------------------

Comments, links, photos, and videos are welcome on all Returning Veterans Project social media platforms. All postings should be relevant to the community of veterans, service members, military families, and volunteer providers who engage with the Returning Veterans Project.  
  
Any posting can be removed for any of the following reasons, at any time, if they: use obscene, threatening or harassing language; endorse or oppose anyone campaigning for or elected to a political office; disclose information that is confidential by law or regulation; promote or advocate illegal activity; violate copyrights or trademarks; or are commercial advertising, unsolicited self-promotion, SPAM, or solicitations. All users, including page administrators, are subject to the terms of service of each Returning Veterans Project social media site and this policy. Comments posted here do not represent the opinions of the Returning Veterans Project.

Personal Information
--------------------

It is the policy of The Returning Veterans Project to respect the privacy of our program participants, volunteers, members, and the people doing business through our services. Personal information presented here WILL NOT be sold, traded, loaned, published, or distributed by any other means to any party other than the Returning Veterans Project.

Security
--------

This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. We store client information in secure databases protected with a variety of access controls. The data is accessed only for the purposes specified in this privacy statement.

Cookies
-------

Our websites use “cookies”. A cookie is a small text file that permits us to recognize your browser in order to customize your experience or permit you access to restricted areas. Cookies do not contain personal information.

IP Address
----------

Your Internet Protocol (“IP”) address is usually associated with the place from which you enter the Internet, like your Internet Service Provider, your company or your University. We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, gather broad demographic information, and administer our websites.

Opt-Out
-------

This site gives clients and members the following options for removing their information from our databases to disallow future communication or to discontinue our services.

* You may remove your own email address from our e-blast/e-news lists by clicking on the opt-out links provided in our automated e-blasts.
* You may also send e-blast removal requests to: [mail@returningveterans.org](mailto:mail@returningveterans.org).

Reporting Bulk-Email Abuse
--------------------------

If you feel the Returning Veterans Project is out of compliance with our own Bulk-Email Policy, you may report bulk email abuse to: [mail@returningveterans.org](mailto:mail@returningveterans.org).

Your Responsibility
-------------------

Should you become aware of a breach of our Privacy and Security policies, or should you suspect a breach at any time, please contact us immediately so that we can respond to your concerns directly.

Email and any attachments are intended solely for the addressee(s) and may contain private, confidential, and/or legally privileged information. If you are not the intended recipient or have received an email in error from the Returning Veterans Project, please alert the sender immediately and permanently delete this message.

Contact Us
----------

If you have any questions about our privacy statement, the practices of our site, or your interactions with this website, please contact us at: [mail@returningveterans.org](mailto:mail@returningveterans.org)  
The Returning Veterans Project: 503-954-2259.

Thank you to [NetRaising](https://netraising.com/) for the original draft language of this privacy statement.

#### [About](https://returningveterans.org/about/ "About")

Newsletter Signup
-----------------

[### Wall of Honor

**In Honor of All the men and women that are serving or have served**  
United States Air Force  
United States Air National Guard  
United States Army  
United States Army National Guard  
United States Coast Guard  
United States Navy  
United States Reserves  
United States Marine Corps  
Submitted by Joseph Lee](https://returningveterans.org/wall-of-honor/ "Visit the Wall of Honor")

Returning Veterans Project

* Returning Veterans Project
* PO Box 14035
* Portland, OR 97293

[DONATE

](https://www3.thedatabank.com/dpg/681/default.asp?formid=donate)

CFC#40798

_The appearance of U.S. Department of Defense (DoD) visual information does not imply or constitute DoD endorsement._

* ©2024 Returning Veterans Project|

https://returningveterans.org/about/privacy-statement/  
Printed 10/21/24 - 2:21:42  
© 2024 Returning Veterans Project
